好吧  该你了
All right, it's your turn.
在ForecastFragment里实现一个CursorLoader
Implement a CursorLoader in the forecast fragment
用来在cursorAdapter里读取cursor
to load the cursor used in the cursor adapter.
当数据发生改变的时候  loader会负责发起重新请求
You want to pass zero in for the flags when you create the cursor adapter as
所以当你创建cursoradapter时  要将flag设置为0
the loader will now be responsible for re-querying when data changes.
而且  这是在ForecastFragment中实现
Also, it's easiest to have ForcastFragment
Loader回调最简单的方法
implement the Loader Callbacks.
如果完成了这些以后
If after you're doing all of this,
你的程序能够显示天气信息  那么你的实现方法就对了
your app still displays the weather, you've probably done it right.
要确定引用到了这里所有类所需的Android
Make sure to check that you are using the support library versions of all of
支持库
our classes.
否则  你的程序讲无法兼容Android 2.3
Otherwise, you won't get Android 2.3 compatibility.
在下面的指导笔记中我已经给出了
I've provided the exact import statements you need to use
确切的导入声明
in the instructor notes below.